Wait a second. I've got a call.
等一下，我有電話。
Hold... Hold... Hold it. Hold it.
I've got a call.
頂…頂住！托住！
我有電話
I can't do this by myself..
You've got to come down here.
我沒辦法自己做這個，你一定得來
I've never been with more than ten kids,
I have 30 kids with me right now.
我從來沒有同時和超過十個小孩在一起過
但現在有三十個小孩跟我在一起！
And I don't know what
I am going to do with them.
然後我不知道我該拿他們怎麼辦
I am trying to keep my eye on them
the whole time I'm here
我嘗試整天注意著他們
and no one showed up.
Not any other parent came,
然後沒有半個人出現，沒有任何人的父母出現！
and I'm by myself.
This is not safe!
我只能靠我自己
但這並不安全！
It's not safe! I'm trying to
protect the kids,
這不安全，我試著保護這些孩子
I just don't know if there's
gonna be an accident.
我只是不知道會不會有突發狀況
Hold on kids! Hold on.
Oh their coming out?!
孩子們等等，等一下，喔！他們要出來了？
Alright guys... call me back, bye.
好…待會打給我，拜拜
Come on, Come on. Walk on down,
walk on down. Come on.
過來，快過來，繼續走，來吧，繼續走
Get over there, get over there,
come on guys
快去那，去那，快點各位
One by one, one by one.
一個接一個，一個接一個
Alright, come with me.
好，跟我走
I'm gonna let you go through alright?
好，現在讓你們過去
Everybody go across,
大家快過
Bea, you stay on the edge
of the curb over there, okay?
碧雅，妳停在那邊的人行道旁好嗎？
Between these two cars.
在這兩輛車之間
That was good, what a relief.
很好！真是鬆了口氣...
Okay, get on through.
Okay, everybody!
很好，跟上
好，大家
Get together, Watch out!
Watch out!
集合集合，小心！
小心！
Watch for your friends! Watch for
your friends! Line up! Line Up!
看看你的朋友在不在！排隊！排隊！
Alright, we're going three more
blocks for pizza at Elliot's house.
好，我們還有三個街區要走才到艾略特披薩店
- Who wants pizza?
- Daddy!
誰想吃披薩？
爸比！
Okay, single file, single file!
好好，排好隊排好隊！
- Daddy, can I hold the balloons?
- Hold the balloons.
爸比，我可以拿氣球嗎？
拿好他們
Guys get back get back!
孩子們，後退後退！
THE BLACK BALLOON
黑色氣球
I see ya…
讓我看看
Hey Ratso!
嘿，藍索
Ratso! Keep your chin up!
藍索！有自信點嘛！
So...?
所以...？
What did he say…
What did Tim say?
他怎說？
提姆他怎麼說？
So... what did he say, he said, uh,
所以..他怎麼說喔…他說…呃...
he said he doesn't want to hear me mention
your name ever again in the office,
他說他再也不想在辦公室聽到我提你的名字
that's what he said.
他是這麼說的
And... what about the show?
那....表演怎麼辦？
The show, no, nothing. He doesn't want
to hear your name, ever again.
表演！不…不怎麼樣。他不想再聽到你的名字，完全不想！
Just move on.
放棄吧！
You didn't talk to him. I don't buy it
for a second that you talked to him.
你沒有跟他說對吧？！我不相信你有跟他說。
No, I didn't. Alright?
對！我沒有，可以嗎？
How could you not talk to him?!
妳怎麼可以沒跟他說？
Because what do you want me to do?
I can't stand up for you!
因為你到底想要我怎樣？
我沒辦法站在你這邊！
10 years ago I got you a job as an intern.
十年前我幫妳找到實習生的工作
What do you want me to say,
what do you want me to do?
你想要我怎說？
你想要我怎麼做？
It is just going to jeopardize
me and my position.
那將會危害到我和我的工作
- I've been there for that long, but..
- Your position!
我在那有一段時間了，但
你的工作？！
- Your position! That's all you care about.
- No, I just don't...
妳的工作！妳只在乎妳的工作！
不，我只是不想...
You were a Pisha
in Queens college TV classes,
妳是Pisha在Queens大學的戲劇班
and I gave you your first break!
而我給了妳第一次的演出機會
And I thank you for that.
And then I worked my way up.
我很謝謝你，後來我也漸漸上手了
And then you became my producer
on a syndicated national show.
然後你變成我在企業聯合國際表演的舞台總監
Can I have one hot dog with mustard
and sauerkraut, please.
麻煩給我一根熱狗加芥末和酸菜
It is insane that I am suspended,
my show is off the air,
我被停止演出實在是太荒謬了
我的表演竟然沒有辦法播出
because I called
President Obama a shvartze.
就因為我叫歐巴馬總統是黑鬼
I mean it's a joke. It's a satire show.
我的意思是這只是一個笑話，這只是一個諷刺的表演
First of all he's not even a shvartze, he's
half a shvartze to be truthful about it.
首先，他並非純黑人，他只是半個，而且這是真的
- Everyone is real upset, alright.
- Yeah, right.
每個人都很生氣好嗎？
喔，是阿
Give me your I.D. Let me just take
the I.D for ten minutes.
給我你的證件，十分鐘就好
- Your gonna eat a hot dog.
- It's not gonna hide your face, Ratso.
你應該吃根熱狗
它沒辦法擋住你的臉好嗎，藍索
They know me there, the security guards
love me! They love Ratso!
他們認識我，那些警衛愛我！他們愛藍索！
If you want, you go march right in!
如果你想要，你就直接走進去吧！
Sorry about that.
喔，我很抱歉
- You have to talk to him.
- I can not be seen with you.
你必須告訴他
我不能被看見跟你在一起
Wait wait, look at this!
This is a message from god!
等等，看看這個
這是來自上帝的訊息
Here, do me a favor.
Take this balloon.
那這樣，幫我一個忙
拿著這個氣球
Bring this to Tim.
把它交給提姆
Tell him this is a gift from Ratso
and he wants his JOB BACK!
告訴他這是藍索送的禮物，然後他想要回他的工作
You know what, I don't think so, they're
gonna think it's a death threat.
你知道嗎？我不這麼認為，他們會覺得這是個死亡威脅
I've got to get back to work.
我必須回去工作了
Go, go back to your little cubicle
with the little robots up there.
那就去阿，回你那小到不行的隔間還有機器人在那邊勒
Yeah, you don't owe me anything,
you are replaceable, I'm the talent!
是阿，你沒欠我任何事情
你是可被取代的，我才是那個有天份的人
That's right! That's right.
Look Ratso,
好，你是對的，對的
藍索，聽著！
I love you as a human being
but I hate you as a person, alright?
身為人類我愛你但身為一個人我討厭你，可以嗎？！
My mother said that too!
我的媽媽也這麼說勒！
Get the f... off.
真是去你.....算了
What?
什麼？
What are there, cameras?
那理有什麼？攝影機？
Where are the cameras?
This is ridiculous.
這裡怎麼可能會有攝影機？
這真是愚蠢至極
Alright, I guess weíre together now babe.
是阿，我想我們現在在一起，寶貝
When I was a kid, my father and I
took a trip down south,
當我小的時候，我的父親和我一起往南旅行
and we stopped to go to the bathroom.
And there were like,
途中我們停下來去上廁所
然後那裡似乎有…
4 bathrooms.
四間廁所
Men white, men colored.
分成男性白人和有色人種
Female white, female colored.
和女性白人和有色人種
I mean I am the furthest thing
from being a racist.
我的意思是我和種族主義者是完全沒關聯的
This is what I want you to do.
這就是我想要你去做的
I want you to go in there and get the
attention of everyone who's there.
我要你進到那，然後抓住他們的注意
Then I am going to come in behind you.
Go right to the security camera, block it!
然後我會跟在你後面進去
你直接去監視器那擋住它
I'm gonna come in, do my thing,
split, then you come out with me.
之後我會進去，把事情做完後就溜走
然後你跟著我出來
Come on, let's go.
來，走吧
Get in!
進去吧
You okay buddy?
Let's get out of here.
兄弟你還好吧？
我們離開這裡吧
Jennie! Jennie! Jennie!
珍妮，珍妮，珍妮
Seriously, you're so persistent, what is...?
說真的，你也太固執了吧，那是...？
- A peace offering!
- No.. what!?
-一個友好的禮物
-不會吧…真的假的？！
This is you! It's beautiful!
I got you this dress.
這是你，很美吧
我買了這條洋裝給妳
No you didn't.
I don't believe you!
不可能，你才沒有
我才不相信你呢
- 1500 Dollars baby!
- Get out of town!
-寶貝，1500元
-你開玩笑的吧！
- It is so you.
- You got that for me?
-這多適合妳阿
-你買給我的？？
- Yes.
- God, it's so beautiful…
-是的
-天阿，這真是美麗...
but.. what is that?
但…那是甚麼？
That's the security tag.
這是防盜磁扣耶！
Ratso you stole it.
藍索你用偷的！
It's still 1500 dollars!
他仍要1500元耶
- Come on, give me a break Ratso!
- It's so you!
-天阿，藍索，真不敢相信你這麼做
-但這真的很適合妳耶
- Get outta here!
- Jennie please take it! Please!
-給我走開
-珍妮拜託妳收下吧，拜託
Come on! Let's go!
來吧，我們走吧！
- Aww, come on! Kylie.
- Don't be rude.
-噢～凱莉，快啦
-不要這麼無禮
- Kylie apologize to Pat.
- Look up there.
-凱莉快跟沛特道歉
-快看那邊
I think that's that "Fluffer Nutter"
that you used to have, right?
我想那是妳曾經吃過的"Fluffer Nutter"，對吧？
She's out in the woods now! That's her!
她現在就在樹林裡！她在那！
- Where?
- Look... Just run down here…
-在哪裡？
-看…直直往上看
- I don't see him.
- and you'll see she's right up in the tree.
-我沒看見
-你會看見她在樹上
- See where that knot is in the tree?
- Just go ahead.
-看見那個在樹上的結了嗎？
-去吧
- It's right above there.
- Come on now, give me some.
-他就在那正上面
-快過來，給我嚐些甜點吧
Mom! Stop!
媽咪！給我停下來！
Sorry, I'm stopping.
抱歉，我不做
Don't touch me!
不要碰我！
Oh, it's a balloon!
歐，是個氣球
Get it!
快去抓住它
Get it! It's going down there.
It's going down.
抓住它！他往那邊飛了
他降在那了
Stop! You told me
you were going to stop.
停止！你告訴我你不會做的
- I'm sorry.
- And you know what?
-很抱歉
-然後妳知道嗎？
Your little favorite dream balloon
over there is going!
你喜愛的小小夢想氣球要飛走了
Ok…
好，好
- That's rude, and you know what, Kylie?
- You've really got to tell her.
-那很失禮，然後凱莉，你知道嗎？
-你真該告訴她！
Go pop it. Pop it. Get it.
去抓住它！快去！抓住它！
Go on, have fun.
快去吧，玩得愉快
Today is my beautiful day.
今天是我美好的一天
I am hungry. You hungry?
我餓了，你呢？
Mustafa, why you no pick up the
phone. I want to speak to you.
莫司特凡，你怎麼沒接電話？我有話要說。
I'm gonna come get you.
I come get you.
我在路上要去見你
我要去找你
Mustafa! Mustafa!
莫司特凡！莫司特凡！
What do you want? I'm working!
你想要幹嘛？我正在工作！
Ok, ok. Give me one minute,
wait one minute.
好，好，給我一分鐘
等我一下
You always come to my restaurant,
what do you want from me?
你總是出現在這
你到底想要幹嘛？
Why you no pick up the phone?
What I did to you? You're my son!
你為甚麼不接電話？
我有做了甚麼嗎？！你是我的兒子！
I'm about to get fired! I'm not even
supposed to be out here right now.
我會被開除的！我現在甚至不該出現在這
- I brought you my friend.
- What's his name?
-我帶了我的朋友來見你
-他叫甚麼？
Jessica!
潔西卡！
Hi, but you can't always be over here.
你好
但你不能總是在這出現
I am so hungry, give me some food.
我真的很餓，給我些吃的吧
You always come here for food,
you never ask how I am.
你總是來討食物吃，你從不問我過的怎樣
Please…
拜託嘛～
Please... please I am hungry.
拜託～～我真的很餓
Alright. You know what?
好吧，這樣吧
Meet me five minutes later at the back.
五分鐘後在後面見我
It's a little bit around there somewhere.
某個在這附近的地方
- Here, now get outta here.
- You don't want me to say something?
-給你，立刻給我出去
-你都不要我說甚麼嗎？
Please go.
拜託，走開
Please leave me alone.
拜託讓我一個人靜靜吧
Please... stay here.
拜託…乖乖待在這
THE BLACK BALLOON
黑色氣球